Exercise 1-4, pure sound. Let's put this in context. Using the AH sound, repeat the
following sounds. Don't worry about what it means. Just repeat the sounds in a
deep, confident voice. That little upside-down E sounds like UH. One. Bah, Bloss,
Dis, Job. Two. Scott taught a lot. Three, Don bought a bike. At this point, you may
be thinking, what the heck is this? It's nonsense. It doesn't even look like
English. I really need to know what I'm saying, and I don't know what this means.
This is gibberish, and I might just sound like a fool here. I need the confidence of
understanding what I'm saying. I'm afraid I'll sound completely foolish. I'm not
confident with this because it's so different from what I've been taught. I
just want to see what it looks like in regular English.